[
  {
    "questionNo": 1,
    "question": "Ella and Jack have 16 napkins and find 10 more. How many napkins do they have in total?<br>[16 + 10 = ?]",
    "options":["1","6","","","",""],
    "answers": ["1","6","1","0","2","6"]
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 2,
    "question": "Ella has 14 balloons and Jack has 23 balloons. What’s the total number of balloons?<br>[14 + 23 = ?]",
    "options":["","","2","3","",""],
    "answers": ["1","4","2","3","3","7"]
    
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 3,
    "question": "There are 13 party hats and they find 16 more. How many party hats are there altogether?<br>[13 + 16 = ?]",
    "options":["1","","","6","",""],
    "answers": ["1","3","1","6","2","9"]
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 4,
    "question": "Jack has 54 party bags and finds 45 more. What’s the total number of party bags?<br>[54 + 45 = ?]",
    "options":["5","4","","","",""],
    "answers": ["5","4","4","5","9","9"]
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 5,
    "question": "Ella finds 31 plates and discovers 12 more in the cupboard. How many plates are there in total?<br>[31 + 12 = ?]",
    "options":["","1","1","","",""],
    "answers": ["3","1","1","2","4","3"]
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 6,
    "question": "They have 40 cups and find 16 more in the kitchen. What’s the total number of cups?<br>[40 + 16 = ?]",
    "options":["4","","","6","",""],
    "answers": ["4","0","1","6","5","6"]
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 7,
    "question": "Ella and Jack count 20 gift boxes and find 28 more in the storage room. How many gift boxes do they have now?<br>[20 + 28 = ?]",
    "options":["2","0","","","",""],
    "answers": ["2","0","2","8","4","8"]
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 8,
    "question": "They start with 26 party streamers and find 11 more. How many streamers are there altogether?<br>[26 + 11 = ?]",
    "options":["","","1","1","",""],
    "answers": ["2","6","1","1","3","7"]
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 9,
    "question": "Ella finds 8 birthday candles and discovers 11 more in a drawer. How many birthday candles are there altogether?<br>[8 + 11 = ?]",
    "options":["","","1","1","",""],
    "answers": ["0","8","1","1","1","9"]
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 10,
    "question": "Ella and Jack have 15 juice drinks and buy 14 more from the store. How many juice drinks do they have in total?<br>[15 + 14 = ?]",
    "options":["1","","","4","",""],
    "answers": ["1","5","1","4","2","9"]
  }
]
